<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OpticalFileTransfer</string>

    <string name="upload_mode_switch_text">Tryb wysyłania plików</string>
    <string name="download_mode_switch_text">Tryb pobierania plików</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Ustawienia</string>
    <string name="draw_blink_encourage_new_transmission">Czekam na nową transmisję..</string>
    <string name="draw_blink_warning_header_not_detected">Nie wykryto sekwencji startowej. </string>
    <string name="draw_blink_started_header_detection">Przygotowuję transmisję..</string>
    <string name="draw_blink_detected_file1">Wykryto plik: </string>
    <string name="draw_blink_detected_file2">Czekam na dane..</string>
    <string name="draw_blink_failed_header_detection">Nie udało się wykryć startu transmisji, spróbuj ponownie..</string>
    <string name="draw_blink_failed_data_detection">Błąd transmisji pliku : </string>
    <string name="draw_blink_succeeded_data_detection">Pomyślnie zapisano plik : </string>
    <string name="draw_blink_pending_async">Przetwarzam plik, proszę czekać.. </string>
    <string name="draw_progress_chunk_name">Szum - fragment</string>





    <string name="menu_string_about">O programie</string>
    <string name="menu_string_settings">Ustawienia</string>
    <string name="menu_string_privacypolicy">Polityka prywatności</string>
    <string name="menu_string_help">Pomoc</string>

    <string name="info_err_selection">Maksymalny błąd (%) : </string>
    <string name="info_qrsize_selection">rozmiar QR (bajty) : </string>
    <string name="info_qrsize_selection2">bajtów</string>
    <string name="info_start_seq_time">Czas sekwencji startowej (s) : </string>
    <string name="resulting_upload_speed">Maksymalna prędkość wysyłania : </string>
    <string name="info_button_restore_default_settings">Przywróć ustawienia domyślne</string>
    <string name="chceck_blurshader">Efekt rozmycia podglądu</string>


    <string name="empty_directory">Pusty katalog</string>
    <string name="storage_removed">Pamięć została odmontowana lub usunięta.</string>
    <string name="choose_file">Wybierz plik</string>
    <string name="error_selecting_file">Błąd wybierania pliku</string>
    <string name="internal_storage">Pamięć wewnętrzna</string>
    <string name="fileread_failed_descr1">Plik </string>
    <string name="fileread_failed_descr2"> nie może być odczytany - prawdopodobnie brak uprawnień odczytu. </string>

    <string name="help_donotshowagaintick">Nie pokazuj ponownie</string>
    <string name="help_title">Pomoc</string>

    <string name="start_sequence_string">Sekwencja startowa : </string>
    <string name="start_sequence_upload_file_desc">Wysyłanie sekwencji startowej pliku : </string>
    <string name="upload_file_desc_string">Wysyłanie pliku : </string>
    <string name="ask_for_new_file_selection_to_upload">Wybierz plik do wysłania</string>
    <string name="title_filebrowse">Przeglądaj odebrane pliki</string>

    <string name="title_choose">Wybierz</string>
    <string name="title_choose_dict_file">Wybierz folder</string>
    <string name="dialog_ok">Zaznacz</string>
    <string name="dialog_cancel">Anuluj</string>
    <string name="title_choose_folder">Wybierz folder</string>
    <string name="title_choose_filetosend">Wybierz plik do wysłania</string>
    <string name="dump_folder_descr">Folder zapisu plików</string>


    <string name="failed_writability_test1">Cannot write to location </string>
    <string name="failed_writability_test2">, perhaps mounted readonly ? Transmission will likely fail. You might want to restart system.</string>

    <string name="upload_file_finalizing_msg">Kończenie pliku, proszę poczekać..</string>

    <string name="ask_folder_choose">Wybierz folder zapisu plików</string>



    <string name="helpd1">Use this app to receive/send small files as the stream of QR frames
        through the phone\'s camera.

        You can generate file QR stream from this app or also the
        desktop PC - see
    Windows and Linux programs for uploading files.</string>

    <string name="helpd2">
        Tips for successfull transmission :
    </string>

    <string name="helpd3">
        1. Keep the camera straight - avoid tilting.
    </string>

    <string name="helpd4">
        2. Make sure camera focus correctly - if not, try waving hand quickly in front of it, or tap the screen
        to request autofocus.
    </string>

    <string name="helpd5">
        3. Keep the highlight green if you can. The more green the highlight gets, the less error is generated, and higher the chance that the
        transmission will succeed. Observe also the noise bar during transmission - avoid getting it fully red
        when the chunk changes.
    </string>

    <string name="helpd6">
        4. Try to capture significant part of the start sequence as well - without it the transmission will not even start.
    </string>

    <string name="defaultButtonMinus">-</string>
    <string name="defaultButtonPlus">+</string>

    <string name="text_content_q1">This sets the Frames Per Seconds (FPS) of the generated QR stream,
        that the decoder tries to keep. Lower value gives slower transmission, but makes it easier
        to ever succeed for older phones with slower camera, or under low light
    conditions. For newer ones, you can try with about 20FPS and see if the transmission
    will succeed. </string>

    <string name="text_content_q2">This sets the amount of redundancy that the frame producer will generate.
        With higher value, the transmission is less likely to fail, but the transmission speed will be
    lower as well. If the noise bar during transmission reception is often green for you when the chunk number increases,
        then you
    can afford to lower this value to increase the transfer speed.</string>

    <string name="text_content_q3">This sets the size of each produced QR frame. Bigger value allows to
    obtain faster transmission, although on my phone I had serious trouble to finish transmission when going above
    750.</string>

    <string name="text_content_q4">This sets the time in seconds, that the initializing startup sequence
    is displayed in the frame producer. It is neccssary to capture at least some fragment of this startup
    sequence to allow proper initialization on the receiver end. Bigger value gives the receiver
    more time to position phone camera to capture stream.</string>



    <string name="link_win">"http://wrobel.wroclaw.pl/opticalfiletransfer/en/win/index.html"</string>
    <string name="link_lin">"http://wrobel.wroclaw.pl/opticalfiletransfer/en/lin/index.html"</string>


    <string name="privpolicy_tilte">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacypolicy1">
        The privacy policy for this app can be found under this link, but it is also presented here below:
        \n\n
        \tThis application does not collect or store any of your data. It only uses the camera to capture
        the stream of QR frames in order to recreate as a file. So it needs camera system permission and
        both the permission to read and write to the file storage - only to do the file transmission.
        No other usage of files occurs other than to do the transmission.\n
        This application also requires permission for system setting write. It only needs to use those system settings permission
        in order to brighten up the screen at the time when file is being transmitted as a stream of QR frames and
        go back to original brightness after it has finished - that lets the receiver camera pick up the image more easily.
        No other system settings other than this brightness manipulation are changed.


        This app uses the Google\'s advertisement services to display the advertisement banner in the
        free version of this app. It might collect some of your data - see the Google privacy policy.
        In order to use this ad services, this app in its free
        version requires permission to network. It does not, however use the network for any other purpose
        than delivering ads through the Admob service. In the non-free version, the network permission are
        not necessary, since there is no ads.


        Links to Other Sites

This app contains links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site.
        Note that these external sites are not operated by me.
        Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites.
        I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

        This application can also request some action from other applications, like opening a file by some external application.
        No information other than query terms are passed to the intent then (like in the case of opening a file or link, only the
        link or file path and mimetype is passed to the external application - nothing else) - so the privacy policy of this external apps
        should be looked up then.

    </string>

    <string name="linkifystr1">Google privacy policy</string>
    <string name="linkifyval1">https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/</string>
    <string name="linkifystr2">under this link</string>
    <string name="linkifyval2">http://wrobel.wroclaw.pl/opticalfiletransfer/en/privacypolicy.html</string>



    <string name="menu_settingfragment_text">

    5 02:23:33.192 10392-10392/? I/art: Late-enablin</string>

</resources>
